[
  { "front": "der Hund", "back": "dog" },
  { "front": "die Katze", "back": "cat" },
  { "front": "der Vogel", "back": "bird" },
  { "front": "die Maus", "back": "mouse" },
  { "front": "die Ratte", "back": "rat" },
  { "front": "das Pferd", "back": "horse" },
  { "front": "die Kuh", "back": "cow" },
  { "front": "die Ziege", "back": "goat" },
  { "front": "das Schaf", "back": "sheep" },
  { "front": "das Schwein", "back": "pig" },
  { "front": "der Frosch", "back": "frog" },
  { "front": "die Schlange", "back": "snake" },
  { "front": "die Eidechse", "back": "lizard" },
  { "front": "der Bär", "back": "bear" },
  { "front": "der Löwe", "back": "lion" },
  { "front": "der Tiger", "back": "tiger" },
  { "front": "der Elefant", "back": "elephant" },
  { "front": "das Känguru", "back": "kangaroo" },
  { "front": "das Krokodil", "back": "crocodile" },
  { "front": "der Affe", "back": "monkey" },
  { "front": "der Pinguin", "back": "penguin" },
  { "front": "der Fuchs", "back": "fox" },
  { "front": "der Wolf", "back": "wolf" },
  { "front": "das Reh", "back": "deer" },
  { "front": "das Huhn", "back": "chicken" },
  { "front": "die Ente", "back": "duck" },
  { "front": "die Gans", "back": "goose" },
  { "front": "der Schwan", "back": "swan" },
  { "front": "der Adler", "back": "eagle" },
  { "front": "die Taube", "back": "pigeon" },
  { "front": "der Hahn", "back": "rooster" },
  { "front": "der Truthahn", "back": "turkey" },
  { "front": "das Kamel", "back": "camel" },
  { "front": "das Nashorn", "back": "rhinoceros" },
  { "front": "das Nilpferd", "back": "hippopotamus" },
  { "front": "der Delfin", "back": "dolphin" },
  { "front": "der Wal", "back": "whale" },
  { "front": "der Hai", "back": "shark" },
  { "front": "die Qualle", "back": "jellyfish" },
  { "front": "die Biene", "back": "bee" },
  { "front": "die Ameise", "back": "ant" },
  { "front": "die Spinne", "back": "spider" },
  { "front": "die Fliege", "back": "fly" },
  { "front": "die Mücke", "back": "mosquito" },
  { "front": "die Schildkröte", "back": "turtle" },
  { "front": "der Fasan", "back": "pheasant" },
  { "front": "der Igel", "back": "hedgehog" },
  { "front": "das Eichhörnchen", "back": "squirrel" },
  { "front": "der Maulwurf", "back": "mole" },
  { "front": "die Krabbe", "back": "crab" },
  { "front": "die Qualle", "back": "jellyfish" }
]
